{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 5,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ is blue and fuzzy.",
          "answer": "blanket"
        },
        { "prompt": "One red rose _____________ opened.", "answer": "blossom" },
        {
          "prompt": "Use the _____________ to scoop some water.",
          "answer": "dipper"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Karen liked to visit _____________ lands.",
          "answer": "distant"
        },
        { "prompt": "We often have _____________ weather.", "answer": "foggy" },
        { "prompt": "We found a bird _____________.", "answer": "fossil" },
        {
          "prompt": "Scott is a _____________ of the club.",
          "answer": "member"
        },
        { "prompt": "She _____________ and said, “Yes.”", "answer": "nodded" },
        {
          "prompt": "The city _____________ created this park.",
          "answer": "planner"
        },
        { "prompt": "We used _____________ forks.", "answer": "plastic" },
        { "prompt": "Thunder _____________ in the sky.", "answer": "rumbles" },
        { "prompt": "The statue was _____________.", "answer": "slender" },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is my favorite season.",
          "answer": "summer"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Do not _____________ the cherry pits.",
          "answer": "swallow"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The old _____________ is from Egypt.",
          "answer": "tablet"
        },
        { "prompt": "Inez loves _____________ movies.", "answer": "thriller" },
        {
          "prompt": "Our car was stuck in _____________.",
          "answer": "traffic"
        },
        { "prompt": "_____________ to my new house.", "answer": "welcome" },
        { "prompt": "Wes climbed the _____________ tree.", "answer": "willow" },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ answered questions.",
          "answer": "witness"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Her dream is to become _____________.",
          "answer": "famous"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Planes use _____________ to navigate.",
          "answer": "radar"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "My dad used a _____________ to shave.",
          "answer": "razor"
        },
        { "prompt": "The hotel had a _____________.", "answer": "vacancy" },
        {
          "prompt": "Donna stood _____________ the statue.",
          "answer": "beside"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Miguel’s story was _____________ belief.",
          "answer": "beyond"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Knights vow to _____________ their king.",
          "answer": "defend"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The traffic accident caused a _____________.",
          "answer": "delay"
        },
        { "prompt": "We _____________ fair treatment.", "answer": "demand" },
        { "prompt": "Firefighters _____________ fires.", "answer": "prevent" },
        {
          "prompt": "The surprise party is a _____________.",
          "answer": "secret"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The president can _____________ new rules.",
          "answer": "veto"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ have thick, shaggy coats.",
          "answer": "bison"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Sandy is a professional scuba _____________.",
          "answer": "diver"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Have you tried the hot apple _____________?",
          "answer": "cider"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ at the library helps us read.",
          "answer": "silence"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Jake’s rabbit sniffed the _____________.",
          "answer": "clover"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We had _____________ about it before.",
          "answer": "spoken"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The police found the _____________ painting.",
          "answer": "stolen"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There is a red _____________ in the garden.",
          "answer": "tulip"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "A jellyfish doesn’t have a _____________!",
          "answer": "brain"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I took the _____________ ten flights up.",
          "answer": "staircase"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "That land is in the king’s _____________.",
          "answer": "domain"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The artist received a lot of _____________ .",
          "answer": "praise"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "My _____________ helps me get into shape.",
          "answer": "trainer"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I like eating _____________ for breakfast.",
          "answer": "oatmeal"
        },
        { "prompt": "We sat _____________ the oak tree.", "answer": "beneath" },
        {
          "prompt": "Please do not _____________ what I said.",
          "answer": "repeat"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I will _____________ my secret to you.",
          "answer": "reveal"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "How can we _____________ school spirit?",
          "answer": "increase"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The mouse had to _____________ past the sleeping cat.",
          "answer": "sneak"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "He likes to _____________ about his grades.",
          "answer": "boast"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The captain kept the ship _____________.",
          "answer": "afloat"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We could hear the frog’s loud _____________.",
          "answer": "croak"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Water is a _____________ made of hydrogen and oxygen.",
          "answer": "compound"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There is a _____________ on all jewelry.",
          "answer": "discount"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The jet was built for high-_____________ travel.",
          "answer": "speed"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The doctor rolled up her _____________.",
          "answer": "sleeve"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Our dog helped guard the _____________ .",
          "answer": "sheep"
        },
        { "prompt": "We saw the _____________ at the zoo.", "answer": "baboon" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "The _____________ stayed open late.", "answer": "grocer" },
        {
          "prompt": "I’m looking for a red _____________ .",
          "answer": "pepper"
        },
        { "prompt": "The _____________ cut Sam’s hair.", "answer": "barber" },
        {
          "prompt": "Every fourth _____________ likes recess.",
          "answer": "grader"
        },
        { "prompt": "_____________ bears have thick fur.", "answer": "Polar" },
        {
          "prompt": "A tugboat pulled an oil _____________ .",
          "answer": "tanker"
        },
        { "prompt": "Bret met the band’s _____________ .", "answer": "singer" },
        {
          "prompt": "We wanted to _____________ the contest.",
          "answer": "enter"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The skunk had a strong _____________ .",
          "answer": "odor"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I bought my dog a new _____________ .",
          "answer": "collar"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ on my jacket is stuck.",
          "answer": "zipper"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I added _____________ to the clown’s face.",
          "answer": "powder"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The icy streets were a _____________ .",
          "answer": "danger"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I put _____________ cheese on my sandwich.",
          "answer": "cheddar"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Pink is a _____________ color for hats.",
          "answer": "popular"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I saw boats docked in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "harbor"
        },
        { "prompt": "The ship dropped _____________ .", "answer": "anchor" },
        {
          "prompt": "We took the _____________ to the top floor.",
          "answer": "elevator"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mrs. Garcia has one _____________ .",
          "answer": "daughter"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ was thrilled to win.",
          "answer": "victor"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I have a _____________ in my shoe.", "answer": "pebble" },
        {
          "prompt": "She was _____________ about winning.",
          "answer": "humble"
        },
        { "prompt": "Can we _____________ our score?", "answer": "double" },
        {
          "prompt": "Buying the used toaster was a _____________.",
          "answer": "gamble"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I had _____________ finishing the project.",
          "answer": "trouble"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "My _____________ lives in New Zealand.",
          "answer": "uncle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Sew this with a _____________ and thread.",
          "answer": "needle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Ada played a _____________ in the band.",
          "answer": "fiddle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Sam wanted to _____________ with his dog.",
          "answer": "cuddle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "My baby sister is in her _____________ .",
          "answer": "cradle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There are monkeys in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "jungle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I ate a _____________ slice of cheese.",
          "answer": "single"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The statue was made of _____________ .",
          "answer": "marble"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "It was fun to _____________ through the park.",
          "answer": "ramble"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "It was a hard problem to _____________ .",
          "answer": "tackle"
        },
        { "prompt": "Emma sprained her _____________ .", "answer": "ankle" },
        {
          "prompt": "I have a _____________ on my cheek.",
          "answer": "freckle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Katie’s belt _____________ was shiny.",
          "answer": "buckle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The coach wanted us to _____________ .",
          "answer": "hustle"
        },
        { "prompt": "Try not to _____________ the string.", "answer": "tangle" }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
